So what I want to do in this video is style and add
在本视频中 我将设置样式
some UI to this undetermined section right here.
并在此处的 undetermined 部分添加一些 UI
So what we'll do is let's just set the status to undetermined that we can see this,
将此 status 设为 undetermined 以便看到此状态
and then I'm going to import a few things.
然后导入一些内容
Let's get TouchableOpacity in here,
在这里导入 TouchableOpacity
as well as StyleSheets.
以及 StyleSheet
We're also going to import foundation from our expo icons.
并从 expo 图标中导入 Foundation
And then finally, let's go and get some colors.
最后获取一些颜色
We'll get purple, as well as whites. All right.
我们将获取 purple 以及 white
So what I'm going to do is just paste in some styles here
因为在这门课程中 我已经多次设置样式
because you've seen me do enough styles in this course.
所以直接在这里粘贴一些样式
So we have a container, a center which is just
我们设置了 container 以及 center
centering everything horizontally and vertically.
center 只是让一切水平和垂直居中
A button, which is purple,
然后是一个 button 背景色为紫色
looks nice, as well as some button text.
此外还有 buttonText
So what we're going to do now is inside of undetermined,
转到 undetermined 内
instead of just saying undetermined,
这里不再设为 undetermined
what we can do is,
而是添加 styles.center
let's add styles.center, so we want to center this both horizontally and vertically.
使其水平和垂直居中
And then, we will have the foundation icon.
然后添加 Foundation 图标
Name is going to be alert,
name 设为 alert
because we're going to say,
因为我们要询问
why did you deny us?
为何拒绝授予权限
You should have accepted us so that we can show you this cool UI.
你应该接受权限请求 这样我们就能显示这个很酷的 UI
So what we'll do now is we will do just that and we will say you
现在我们将输出这一消息：
need to enable location services for this app.
You need to enable location services for this app.
And then here, what we will do is we will have our button, onPress.
然后在这里添加按钮 输入 onPress
We will create a method called,
我们将创建一个方法
askPermission, which will do just that.
叫做 askPermission 它将请求权限
Style is going to be styles.button.
将 style 设为 styles.button
And then inside of this,
然后在这里面
we can say, enable.
输入 Enable
And we want to style this with the styles.button text,
将 style 设为之前创建的 styles.buttonText
which we created earlier. This looks good.
看起来不错
Let's go ahead and create just a placeholder for askPermission right now.
暂时为 askPermission 创建一个占位符
And now, what should happen is if everything is good,
现在 看看应用效果 一切正常
when we click on live we get this UI here.
当我们点击 Live 出现了这个 UI
So this is the UI again for if the status is undetermined,
如果 status 为 undetermined 就会出现该 UI
we're going to go ahead and say, hey,
我们将提醒用户
you need to enable location services for this application.
嘿 你需要为此应用启用位置服务
Click here, and eventually what that should do is open up a dialog saying,
点击此按钮 最终将打开一个对话框
hey, go ahead and get this app permission to track your location.
提示：嘿 请授予此应用权限以便跟踪你的位置信息